platgroupng.com 2019-06-26

# Privacy Policy | Plat Technologies Limited

## Our Commitment to You

Plat Technologies Limited respects your privacy and is committed to protecting personal information collected from you through our website. This privacy policy governs the way we collect and use information, and by using the services on our website ('Services') you agree to be bound by this policy. All references within this policy to 'we/us/our' refer to Plat Technologies Limited.

## Information We Collect

When you use the Services you will have the option to provide us with personal information, such as your email address, so that we may keep you informed. We use this information only in response to your requests and to provide the Services.

When visiting our website, we may place one or more cookies (a small file that is stored by your browser to recognise you and store your preferences) on your computer. This helps us to improve our Services by personalising information you may want. You may adjust the settings on your browser to refuse cookies but some of the Services may not work if you do so. We may also log information from your computer including the existence of cookies, your IP address and information about your browser program in order to allow us to diagnose problems, administer and track your usage of the Services.

## How We Use Information

We use the information we collect to provide the Services and to communicate with you. We do not rent or sell personal information and will only share your information in the following circumstances:

  1. When you have consented or directed us to share the information.
  2. With service providers or affiliate companies who perform services on our behalf.
  3. In order to satisfy any requirement under the law or to protect our rights or prevent any concerns relating to fraud or security.
  4. In the event of a merger or sale of all or part of our business whereby personal information may be transferred as an asset of the business.

We may share with third parties aggregate information or information that does not personally identify individuals.

## Communicating With You

If you prefer not to receive emails about our Services, you may opt out of such communications by following the instructions at the bottom of any of our emails.

## Third Parties

We use third parties to serve advertisements on our website and these third parties may use cookies or other means to help measure the effectiveness of their advertisements. Our website may also include links to other unrelated websites and/or contact forms to other unrelated parties which may collect personal information. Our privacy policy does not extend to these third parties or other websites and we recommend that users refer directly to these parties regarding their privacy policies before supplying personal details to these companies.

## Safety and Security

Personal information is processed and stored in our databases and we have taken reasonable steps to secure and protect the information under our control, including establishing processes to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure of this information. However, whilst we make every effort to ensure the security of your information, we are unable to guarantee the protection of the information from misuse, accidental disclosure or unauthorised acts by others. Information provided by you may be stored or processed outside Nigeria.

## Changes to Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time without prior notice to you. Any changes will be posted on our website and become effective at the time of posting. In the event that material changes are made that affect the use or disclosure of your personal information, we will make reasonable efforts to notify you of these changes.

If you have any questions or comments about our privacy policy, please Contact us.

Website Design Web Application Development  
Website Maintenace Services  
Search Engine Optimisation  
ICT Consultancy  
ICT Outsourcing 

**Head Office:** 12, Ilofa Road, GRA, Ilorin

**Telephone:** 234-(0)8020889646

**Email:**[info@platgroupng.com](mailto:info@platgroupng.com)

## Quick Links

News and Events  
Website Design Articles  
Website Design Resources   
Directory of Websites  
Sitemap

~ Student Portal for Tertiary Institutions  
~ Computer Based Testing Software  
~ Epayment Integration Platform (Interswitch and Etranzact)  
~ Results Porcessing Software (Internet/Intranet Based)  
~ e-Library Resource Portal  
~ Student Portal for Primary/Secondary Schools
